wisdomquotesandstories.com 2016-08-26

# Privacy Policy – Wisdom Quotes & Stories

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which We collect, use, maintain and disclose information collected from users of www.wisdomquotesandstories.com website and all services offered.

 **Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site and in connection with other services. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, age, sex, email address etc. and users if so desire may voluntarily submit such information to us.

 **Using collected information**

We may collect and use Users personal information for running a promotion, survey or other Site feature , to send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them, to send periodic emails and respond to their inquiries, questions and/or other requests. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails he is free to inform us accordingly.

 **Protecting personal information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information stored on our Site. We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

 **Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of the third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by them. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any such advertising partners.

 **Changes to this privacy policy**

We have the right to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site,

Please contact us at info@wisdomquotesandstories.com **  
**

Date:- 01 st July 2013
